Guide to the Norman Dorsen Papers TAM.251
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Audio-visual materials.
  - "COURT TV AIRCHECK 7:P-9:P 2/10/92" (VHS), Feb 1992 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_149f2b3c363d91746c9df7874c7a94b0)
  - "COURT TV DORSEN 430p-8p 4-28-92" (VHS), Apr 1992 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_a4143e256a7296e01f3d57bcbc6cb7b7)
  - "COURT TV 8-26-92 NORMAN DORSEN 4:30-8 pm" (VHS), Aug 1992 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_1b588cf317740b72ef50c3b6dc5f5c74)
  - "CTV Guest Norman Dorsen 11A-2:30p 1/21/93" (VHS), Jan 1993 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_660670a33505e2e49e8d073c7b51986e)
  - "CTV NORMAN DORSEN 1/11/93 4-6p" (VHS), Jan 1993 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_07353e5d9d4b6e3a10a26bb34170d811)
  - "CTV Guest NORMAN DORSEN 5p-8p 1/13/93" (VHS), Jan 1993 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_1de695756d2bdd25ee38c8b714162f66)
  - "OPER. RESCUE GUEST TAPE 2/15/93 COURT TV NORMAN DORSEN 2-5p" (VHS), Feb 1993 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_2b3027b34b21acbae2064f375564f23e)
  - "NORMAN DORSEN COURT TV AIR CHECK 5-6-93" (VHS), May 1993 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_b2fddf3f0fc3c13e605eabc813866358)
  - "NORMAN DORSEN COURT TV AIR CHECK 7-14-93" (VHS), Jul 1993 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_e6b2e5be89f3bbf69bf8bacd9b52ef8c)
  - "NORMAN DORSEN COURT TV AIR CHECK 10-14-93" (VHS), Oct 1993 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_b7e7d6d35db62d7264e101347ac8f01c)
  - "ROUNDUP NEWS STORIES 7/11 & 7/21/95" (VHS), Jul 1995 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_ac826dc29255a190c95b4acb9e0fe06a)
  - "ACLU 1995" (VHS) (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_c052c901f4442b7000f09c6218af3155)
  - "Norman Dorsen 4-11-96 Court TV" (VHS), Apr 1996 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_d31ee220c113bf4f5b7035b95d2d18f8)
  - "MR. JUSTICE BRENNAN Produced by Jerry Colbert October 7, 1996 - 10 PM EST on public television stations nationwide" (VHS), Oct 1996 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_2cf870a46d737ebda8e5b09f7af9ec2f)
  - "Inside The Law / NOLA No. 804 / 'International Crimes & International Tribunals' / Part 1 / TRT: 28:30 / Associated Broadcast Consultants, Inc. / 4-14-2000" (VHS), Apr 2000 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_2825cf80faea4f1377a0eadd8625889f)
  - "Inside The Law / NOLA No. 804 / 'International Crimes & International Tribunals' / Part 2 / TRT: 28:30 / Associated Broadcast Consultants, Inc. / 4-14-2000" (VHS), Apr 2000 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_129a8b67f96838b41b4f6aba0f61456d)
  - "3/1/01 Annual Survey Dedication Honoring Norman Dorsen DUPLICATE" (VHS), Mar 2001 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_06624e3702b5fd6e4b75572b276d0b71)
  - Norman Dorsen: Remarks on Gault (DVD), Mar 2003 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_fc79a91003e2166fc948ebf171029f3a)
  - Norman Dorsen: Hays Reunion Dinner (VHS), May 2003 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_afeb0d9b502e7910859f3552acf8679e)
  - Norman Dorsen: Hays Reunion Dinner (DVD), May 2003 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_3535969c434a6aaa42a518078c3ca8f6)